<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items><item><category><value>Rompicapo e puzzle</value></category><desc><value>Play against the best Chinese Chess AI Engineer with 10 levels of difficult in HD graphics or improve your ending skill by solving 280+ built-in postures.</value><value>Note: every posture has a solution :) just try it more, dont give little stars just because it's difficult:P If you're stuck, you can contact me :)</value></desc><link><value>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=vn.vhn.android.VHChineseChess</value></link><title><value>VHChineseChess</value></title></item><item><category><value>Rompicapo e puzzle</value></category><desc><value>Play Chinese Chess Plays against the computer at various difficulty levels.</value><value>*NEW in Market*: Chinese Chess Online!</value><value>The first Chinese Chess game for Android. Moves pieces through touch screen. Plays against the computer at various difficulty levels. Undo/redo by gestures. Load/save game.</value><value>*NEW in V1.0.7*: prevent repetitive moves.</value><value>Enjoy it!</value></desc><link><value>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.cchess</value></link><title><value>Chinese Chess</value></title></item><item><category><value>Rompicapo e puzzle</value></category><desc><value>Xiangqi: l'scacchi cinesi</value><value>Xiangqi: TCC è un nuovo gioco sviluppato da un appassionato di scacchi cinesi. Questa applicazione rimarrà liberamente condiviso. Io contare su giocatori di scacchi cinesi per mandarmi feedback sul design e gameplay. Inviami le idee e le correzioni di lingua, vorrei questa applicazione gioco per essere di qualità molto buona.</value></desc><link><value>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.mdb.android.xiangqi</value></link><title><value>中国象棋 : The Chinese Chess</value></title></item><item><category><value>Rompicapo e puzzle</value></category><desc><value>Acclamata dalla critica la versione di Chinese Chess realizzata dalla ZingMagic, è un'alternativa valida ed interessante alla versione Chess occidentale.</value><value>Come Chess tradizionale, l'obiettivo di questo gioco è di catturare il Re. Hai sette pedine a tua disposizione, ognuna con la sua regola di movimento. La scacchiera includa linee diagonali ed orizzontali, e le pedine si muovono lungo le linee fermandosi dove intersecano. L'area bianca nel mezzo della scacchiera rappresenta il fiume Giallo che divide il Nord ed il Sud della Cina.</value><value>Il motore del gioco è stato realizzato da un programmatore campione di Scacchi cinesi.</value><value>Caratteristiche di gioco:</value><value>* Puoi scegliere di giocare contro il computer o contro un altro giocatore sullo stesso dispositivo.</value><value>* Il motore del gioco è stato realizzato da un programmatore campione di Scacchi cinesi</value><value>* Un’ampia scelta di layout</value><value>* Una varietà di set di pezzi</value><value>* Configurazione pezzi Chinese e Occidentale</value><value>* Funzioni integrali di annullamento e ripetizione di mosse.</value><value>* Mostra ultima mossa.</value><value>* Mostra mosse consentite.</value><value>* Mostra pedine in pericolo.</value><value>* Suggerimenti.</value><value>* Scacchi cinesi è soltanto uno dei bellissimi giochi della nostra collezione di giochi di simulazione, di carte e puzzle, disponibili in diverse lingue per una vasta gamma di piattaforme.</value></desc><link><value>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.zingmagic.chinesechessvfree</value></link><title><value>Scacchi cinesi V - Gratuito</value></title></item><item><category><value>Rompicapo e puzzle</value></category><desc><value>Chinese Chess game with lots of features:</value><value>- One or Two Players game</value><value>- AI can play either color</value><value>- Network games with peers</value><value>- Game rules</value><value>- Configuration of look and feel</value><value>- Multi-language support (English, Simplified and Traditional Chinese)</value><value>- Save/Load</value><value>- Multi-level feature </value><value>Download and join the fun!</value></desc><link><value>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.game.chinesechessfree</value></link><title><value>Chinese Chess Free</value></title></item><item><category><value>Carte e casinò</value></category><desc><value>blackJack</value></desc><link><value>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.DreamFactory.BlackJack</value></link><title><value>blackJack</value></title></item><item><category><value>Rompicapo e puzzle</value></category><desc><value>Cinese Dark Chess è un classico, gioco facile e divertente.</value><value>Dark Scacchi cinesi, o la metà di scacchi, è un bordo di due giocatori del gioco, giocato su una griglia 4x8. La maggior parte dei giochi di ultima tra i dieci ei venti minuti. Si tratta di un gioco sociale, di solito gioca per divertimento, piuttosto che una seria concorrenza. Non preoccuparti per i caratteri cinesi, per i bambini e gli amici stranieri, progettiamo gli scacchi immagine per voi. E 'facile e divertente.</value><value>====================================</value><value>[English Introduction]</value><value>Chinese Dark Chess , or Half Chess, is a two players board game, played on a 4x8 grid. Most games last between ten and twenty minutes. It is a social game, usually played for fun rather than serious competition.</value><value>Don’t worry about the Chinese characters, for children and foreign friends, we design the image chess for you. It is easy and fun.</value><value>We always do our best to test the program while we release it. However, there are various models of mobile phone for Android system. Please kindly Email to us , tell us what step cause bug. We very appreciate your understanding and support.</value></desc><link><value>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.xidea.ChineseDarkChess</value></link><title><value>Scacchi cinesi Dark</value></title></item><item><category><value>Rompicapo e puzzle</value></category><desc><value>The timeless game of intellectual warfare. Are you a grand master in the making?</value><value>★ From Google Play “Top Developer” AI Factory ★</value><value>Chess Free is the best free Chess game on Android! and is currently the highest rated free chess on Android (at time of writing), from the 30+ free chess programs listed.</value><value>★★★★-- rating!: "Chess Free provides a rich and challenging experience of this classic board game, all within the confines of your Android smart-phone. " James Woodcock : Review Journalist (</value><value>http://www.jameswoodcock.co.uk/?p=5427</value><value>)</value><value>Featuring:</value><value>-- 10 play levels (Novice-&gt;Expert)</value><value>This uses intelligent weakening for lower levels. Good for beginners.</value><value>-- Uses Treebeard Chess engine</value><value>(as used in Microsoft's MSN Chess). This has a unique "human-like" style.</value><value>-- "Show CPU Thinking" option</value><value>A unique feature, great for learning chess. This shows which moves the AI is considering.</value><value>-- Chess Stats, Timers, Hints and Handicaps</value><value>Track your career history against each level and improve your rating    </value><value>-- 2 player hot-seat</value><value>Play against your friends!</value><value>-- 4 Chess Boards and 4 Chess Piece Sets</value><value>-- Review game mode</value><value>Step back through your game and see how you won!</value><value>-- Load/Save game files &amp; PGN Export</value><value>-- Designed for both Tablet and Phone</value><value>-- Full Touch screen and trackball support</value><value>-- Support for latest Android 3.X and 4.X action bar for options and menu access</value><value>Supported by unobtrusive Ads.</value><value>*Note: Requested permissions are a requirement of the in-game ads only. The Paid version has no ads, and therefore no permissions beyond writing to SD card.*</value><value>See some of the 10000+ user comments!</value><value>Download the best Chess for Android now!</value></desc><link><value>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=uk.co.aifactory.chessfree</value></link><title><value>Chess Free</value></title></item><item><category><value>Rompicapo e puzzle</value></category><desc><value>Free multiplayer Chinese Chess Online game for Android phones.</value><value>Multiplayer Chinese Chess Online game for Android phones. Operates through touch screen. Intuitive UI to select opponents. Highlights moves on the chessboard. Supports sound effects, vibrate, nudge. No password required.</value><value>*NEW in V1.0.7*: Users can chat when playing.</value><value>Enjoy it!</value></desc><link><value>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.chessquare.cchessonline</value></link><title><value>Chinese Chess Online</value></title></item></items>